flydenver.com 2017-06-01

# Use & Privacy Policies | Denver International Airport

The City and County of Denver Department of Aviation is committed to protecting user privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the Web will not only protect users, but also increase user confidence and ultimately their participation in online activities. At Flydenver.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone and the choices you have regarding our use of and your ability to correct the information. The privacy policy for this site follows:

If you send us an electronic mail message or complete an online feedback form with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information or if you fill out a form that e-mails us this information, we will use the personally identifiable information only to respond to your request and analyze trends. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question.

## Information that we collect for statistical purposes:

We collect information that is used for analysis and statistical purposes to help us best manage the FlyDenver.com site. We automatically collect electronically generated information about your visit to our site, such as the date, type of browser used and technical Internet protocol data. We collect this information about each user session from our user logs and refer to it for statistical purposes.

## Information that you provide us when using our interactive forms and functions:

This information may include such things as name, telephone number and e-mail address.

## Use of cookies

We do not use "persistent" cookies to collect permanent information. (Note: A cookie file contains unique information a Web site can use to track such things as passwords, lists of pages you've visited, and the date when you last looked at a specific page or to identify your session at a particular Web site. A cookie is often used in commercial sites to identify the items selected for a specific shopping cart application.)

We do use "non-persistent" cookies in applications that keep track of a user and make it possible for you to use a function, but this cookie disappears once the use of the function expires.

## Disclosure to third parties

As a governmental agency, we are governed by open records laws. Any information that we receive through the use of our site is subject to the same provisions as information provided on paper. Otherwise, we do not share personal identifying information with any third party without your permission. We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties.

This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information and will not be released to any outside parties unless we are legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings.

## Link Policy

The City and County of Denver Department of Aviation links to other World Wide Web sites in support of our vision to create the optimum travel experience.

The Department of Aviation does not endorse any product or entity for which a link may be provided and the Department of Aviation is not responsible for the content or availability of these outside resources. The Department of Aviation, Denver International Airport, may select links based upon:

  * support of airport functions and business;
  * convenience to the public in their interaction with the airport;
  * economic development within the airport;
  * an affinity or logical nexus with the function or purpose of the airport, and
  * the existence of a direct business relationship with the airport

The website manager reviews all link requests for adherence to these criteria, together with the following considerations:

  * availability of system resources and personnel to monitor and maintain the FlyDenver.com website;
  * the relationship and importance of the link requested to the ordinary and necessary functioning of the airport, and
  * the significance and timeliness of materials contained on the linked site

Denver International Airport reserves the right to deny any link request.

## Customer Use Policy

The City and County of Denver uses many outlets to engage with its citizens and customers, including through social media. Part of this engagement includes the sharing of information between the City and users of official City social media sites. Please be aware that your engagement with the City through social media sites means that you are agreeing to the following:

## Information Collected by the City via Social Media

The City and County of Denver is committed to protecting your individual privacy and securing personal information made available to us when using our official social media sites. The City does not collect or store personal information made available to us via our official social media sites, nor does it provide such information to third-parties. However, it is important to remember that social media sites are public sites. Therefore, you are discouraged from disclosing personal information at any time. The City does collect anonymous, demographic information via the owners of social media sites. This demographic information is used by the City to determine the most effective use of social media.

Certain City sites allow you to sign up to receive periodic communications, such as event notifications, City updates, and reminders for things like street sweeping and trash pickup. The information obtained by these means is strictly used for the purpose identified in the sign-up form.

## Commenting on an Airport Social Media Site

The City and County of Denver Department of Aviation encourages the use of its social media sites as a forum for discussion. However, all official City social media sites are moderated for appropriate content. While comments will not be edited by City personnel, the following types of comments may be deleted:

  * Comments engaging in political activity including advocating for the election or defeat of any individual to elected public office or promoting the passage or defeat of any ballot question or measure
  * Comments promoting or advertising a business or commercial transaction
  * Comments including obscene, threatening or harassing language
  * Comments including personal attacks of any kind
  * Comments that target or disparage any ethnic, racial, age, or religious group, gender, sexual orientation or disability status
  * Comments advocating illegal activity or including the posting of material that violates copyrights or trademarks of others

## Terms of Service of the Host Site

All posting activity on City social media sites is also subject to the Terms of Service (TOS) of the host site. For more information, consult the host website’s TOS.

For additional information regarding the City and County of Denver's online privacy and use policies, visit <http://www.denvergov.org/TermsofUse/tabid/435584/Default.aspx>

## Copyright

While the City and County of Denver Deaprtment of Aviation provides the information on this server to anyone, we retain copyright on all text, graphic images, and other content. This means that you may not: distribute the text or graphics to others without the express written permission of the City and County of Denver Department of Aviation; "mirror" this information on your server without our permission; or modify or re-use the text or graphics on this system. You may print copies of the information for your own personal use and; reference this server from your own documents. Commercial use of the materials is prohibited without the written permission of the City and County of Denver Department of Aviation. In all copies of this information, you must retain this notice and any other copyright notices originally included with such information.

The City and County of Denver reserves all other rights.

Copyright © 2014, City & County of Denver Deaprtment of Aviation
